<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.cpntools.accesscpn.engine.feature"
      label="CPN Tools Simulator for Access CPN"
      version="2.2.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="CPN Tools">

   <description url="http://cpntools.org/accesscpn">
      CPN Tools simulator to be used by Access/CPN
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://cpntools.org/license/simulator">
Copyright © 2010-2012, AIS Group, Eindhoven University of Technology
All rights reserved.

CPN Tools is originally developed by the CPN Group at Aarhus University from 2000 to 2010. The main architects behind the tool are Kurt Jensen, Søren Christensen, Lars M. Kristensen, and Michael Westergaard. From the autumn of 2010, CPN Tools is transferred to the AIS group, Eindhoven University of Technology, The Netherlands.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    All advertising materials mentioning features or use of this software must display the following acknowledgement: “This product includes software developed by the AIS Group, Eindhoven University of Technology and the CPN Group, Aarhus University.”
    Neither the name of the AIS Group, Eindhoven University of Technology, the name of Eindhoven University of Technology, nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AIS GROUP, EINDHOVEN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AS IS AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AIS GROUP, EINDHOVEN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://cpntools.org/license/simulator">
The simulator component of CPN Tools is dual-licensed and can be used either under the GNU General Public License (GPL) version 2 or by the below license, which is a 4-clause BSD license.

4-clause BSD License for CPN Tools Simulator

Copyright © 2010-2012, AIS Group, Eindhoven University of Technology
All rights reserved.

CPN Tools is originally developed by the CPN Group at Aarhus University from 2000 to 2010. The main architects behind the tool are Kurt Jensen, Søren Christensen, Lars M. Kristensen, and Michael Westergaard. From the autumn of 2010, CPN Tools is transferred to the AIS group, Eindhoven University of Technology, The Netherlands.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    All advertising materials mentioning features or use of this software must display the following acknowledgement: “This product includes software developed by the AIS Group, Eindhoven University of Technology and the CPN Group, Aarhus University.”
    Neither the name of the AIS Group, Eindhoven University of Technology, the name of Eindhoven University of Technology, nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AIS GROUP, EINDHOVEN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AS IS AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AIS GROUP, EINDHOVEN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="org.cpntools.accesscpn.engine"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
